<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Homework 2</string>

    <string name="menu_text">Welcome to the Jojo\'s Bizarre Adventure Plot Summary App</string>

    <string name="action_create_order">View Plot Summaries</string>

    <string-array name="menu">
        <item>Part 1: Phantom Blood</item>
        <item>Part 2: Battle Tendency</item>
        <item>Part 3: Stardust Crusaders</item>
        <item>Part 4: Diamond is Unbreakable</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="phantom_blood">
        JoJo\'s Bizarre Adventure volumes 1 to 5. In the 1880s in Great Britain, the young Jonathan
        Joestar meets his new adopted brother Dio Brando, who only wants to usurp Jonathan as heir
        to the Joestar family. However, his attempts are thwarted and he resorts to using an ancient
        Stone Mask which transforms him into a vampire. Jonathan, with Italian Hamon master Will
        A. Zeppeli and former street thug Robert E.O. Speedwagon at his side, must now find a way
        to stop Dio using his newly found affinity for the Ripple martial arts now that Dio\'s
        sights are set on nothing less than world domination.
    </string>

    <string name="battle_tendency">
        JoJo\'s Bizarre Adventure volumes 5 to 12. In New York City in 1938, Joseph Joestar, grandson
        of Jonathan, who has a natural affinity for the Hamon technique, becomes entangled in his
        grandfather\'s destiny when the Pillar Men, supernatural beings of impossible power, awaken
        after failed experiments by Nazi German special forces. Joseph ultimately teams up with
        Caesar Zeppeli, Will\'s grandson, and Caesar\'s teacher Lisa Lisa, a woman mysteriously tied
        to Joseph, to stop the Pillar Men from obtaining a mystical artifact in Lisa Lisa\'s
        possession that will grant them complete immortality and bring about the end of the world
        at their hands, so long as Joseph can master the Hamon technique to beat the Pillar Men in
        a rematch for the antidotes to poisons they implanted in his body.
    </string>

    <string name="stardust_crusaders">
        JoJo\'s Bizarre Adventure volumes 12 to 28. In 1989, Jotaro Kujo, a Japanese high school
        student, places himself in jail because he believes he is possessed by an evil spirit. His
        mother Holly calls on her father Joseph Joestar to talk sense into Jotaro, and with the
        help of his ally the Egyptian fortune teller Mohammed Avdol, reveals that Jotaro has in fact
        developed a supernatural ability known as a Stand that has run through the family due to the
        revival of their ancestor\'s foe Dio. After thwarting an assassination attempt by transfer
        student Noriaki Kakyoin who is under Dio\'s thrall, Jotaro and Joseph discover that Holly is
        dying from her own Stand. Jotaro resolves to hunt down Dio, and Joseph leads him, Avdol,
        and Kakyoin to Egypt, using their Stands to battle more Stand-wielding assassins along the
        way, gaining allies in the French swordsman Jean Pierre Polnareff who wishes to avenge the
        death of his sister, and the stray dog Iggy, before 50 days elapse and Holly dies.
    </string>

    <string name="diamond_is_unbreakable">
        JoJo\'s Bizarre Adventure volumes 29 to 47. In the fictional Japanese town of Morioh in 1999,
        Jotaro arrives to reveal to Josuke Higashikata that he is the illegitimate son of Joseph
        Joestar and to warn him that Morioh is beginning to be filled with Stand users due to a
        mystical Bow and Arrow that bestows Stands on those struck by the arrowheads. After Josuke
        takes revenge on a Stand user who killed his grandfather, he agrees to help Jotaro hunt
        down the holder of the Bow and Arrow, gaining allies in Josuke\'s friend Koichi Hirose, who
        is hit by the arrow, Okuyasu Nijimura, whose brother was using the Arrow until it was stolen
        from him, the famous manga artist Rohan Kishibe, and even his estranged father Joseph
        Joestar. Along the way, the group deals with the various new Stand users throughout Morioh,
        including several of Josuke, Koichi, and Okuyasu\'s classmates, until the death of one of
        their friends leads to the discovery that one of the new Stand users is the serial killer,
        Yoshikage Kira.
    </string>
</resources>
